Only skeleton and rigid body customizations and optimizations, as well as UV recreations, are allowed.

===================
No reuploads.

Do not use it for public adult content and extreme religious propaganda.

Not for commercial use.

For the sake of consistency, changing the model into any non-TDA-styled model is not advised.

The user, not the model creator, will be held fully responsible for any undesirable outcome caused by his or her use of the model.

Model Editing: 神帝宇

Hair：maza

The copyrights of partial model customization resources are owned by miHoYo.



---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

只允許改造，優化骨骼和剛體，重制UV(貼圖在模型表面的位置)
 
 ===================
 請勿二次發佈模型
 
 請勿用於公開性質的18禁，極端宗教宣傳
 
 請勿用於商業用途
 
 考慮到模型的一致性，不太建議改造為其他非TDA式模型
 
 他人使用該模型所造成的一切不良後果，不由模型製作者承擔，請向使用者追究全部責任，
 
 模型編輯：神帝宇
 
 頭髮：maza
 
 改模所用部分素材版權所屬miHoYo


---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

골격과 강체의 개선 및 개조, UV 리메이크만 허용됩니다.

===================
원형 모델 외부 공개를 금지합니다.

공개적인 성적 표현, 극단적 종교 선전을 금지합니다.

상업적 용도 사용을 금지합니다.

모델의 일치성을 위해 다른 TDA식으로의 개조는 권하지 않습니다.

타인의 모델 사용으로 일어난 모든 피해에 대해 모델 제작자는 책임지지 않으며, 사용자에게 모든 책임이 있습니다.

모델 편집:神帝宇

머리: maza

모델 개조에 사용된 모든 소재의 판권은 miHoYo에게 있습니다.